<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolios on Frottage</title>
    <link>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolios on Frottage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +1200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pistis Sophia</title>
      <link>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/pistis-sophia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/pistis-sophia/</guid>
      <description>Prompt gens 1 2 3 4 Sophia is a feminine figure, analogous to the human soul but also simultaneously one of the feminine aspects of God. Gnostics held that she was the syzygy (female twin divine Aeon) of Jesus (i.e. the Bride of Christ), and Holy Spirit of the Trinity. Digital Art 1 2 3 Sophia is the lowest Aeon, or anthropic expression of the emanation of the light of God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bookends of the Book of Life</title>
      <link>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/the-bookends-of-the-book-of-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/the-bookends-of-the-book-of-life/</guid>
      <description>Two perfect syzygies on each end of July. At the second half of 2022. I entered Heaven on the perfect day.
Journal: The Most Surreal Day // Bodacious Blog There&amp;rsquo;s only building up from here.
Welcome to Our World // Bodacious Blog The bookends of the book of life.
The Bookends of Life 1 Two bookends enclose the perfect day. Living in providence 1 2 providence Divine guidance or care. To live out gnosis is to continue trusting in Truth despite chaos all around you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Most Surreal Day</title>
      <link>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/the-most-surreal-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/the-most-surreal-day/</guid>
      <description>Blog https://semiosis.github.io/posts/the-most-surreal-day/ Water, fire and light I bought the glass pendent so I can put Melee&amp;rsquo;s paintings in it to keep her close to me.
I was wearing all black that day and the pendant with the same Gankyl (The wheel of Joy; coloured in with fire, water and light), that I wore when I met the Holy Spirit.
Too much synchronicity Some birds came up to me. I bought a cheese roll for them I gave away all my money Chen&amp;rsquo;s doppelganger Caleb turned up and I talked to him about the Holy Spirit I told him about my meeting with the subconscious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpha Genesis</title>
      <link>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/alpha-genesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/alpha-genesis/</guid>
      <description>My eisegesis https://mullikine.github.io/posts/genesis/ Original poetry https://llamasandmystegosaurus.blogspot.com/2017/05/alpha.html Music to go with it Dalle gens 1 An advent: ancient archangels architect abstract astronomy and arid asteroids. Digital Art 1 All asteroids are amorphous and absent; And all asleep across aquatic anarchy. And astral angels advanced across area. Digital Art 1 Abundant agricultural affluence: azaleas, anise, amaranth. And apples and apricots, almonds and acacias, an arboreal appearance. Digital Art 1 And Almighty asked, Astronomical atmosphere ablaze, aglow, an auroral aubade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Our World</title>
      <link>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/welcome-to-our-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/welcome-to-our-world/</guid>
      <description>My Nana chose this song for my Christening John Grenell died yesterday.
It&amp;rsquo;s country music but I was 0 years old so, not my fault.
Another perfect syzygy in timing.
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 Welcome to my world Won&amp;#39;t you come on in Miracles, I guess Still happen now and then Step into my heart Leave your cares behind Welcome to my world Built with you in mind Knock and the door will open Seek and you will find Ask and you&amp;#39;ll be given The key to this world of mine I&amp;#39;ll be waiting here With my arms unfurled Waiting just for you Welcome to my world Waiting just for you Welcome to my world John Denver Hore, better known by his stage name of John Grenell, was a New Zealand country singer and songwriter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infogetics</title>
      <link>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/infogetics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/infogetics/</guid>
      <description>Prompt gens 1 2 This is a photo of a futuristic LED panel with many buttons with mathematical symbols 1 2 This is a photo of a futuristic dashboard with many LED buttons with mathematical symbols 1 2 This is a photo of a futuristic dashboard with many LED buttons with mathematical symbols. Some look alien in origin </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parakleton; Your Holy Advocate</title>
      <link>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/parakleton/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/parakleton/</guid>
      <description> 1 2 3 4 In the court of God, the Holy Spirit stands with you, and defends you. This is an image of a person standing before God, and the Holy Spirit standing next to them. Digital Art </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pink Cherry Blossoms Splash</title>
      <link>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/pink-cherry-blossoms-splash/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/pink-cherry-blossoms-splash/</guid>
      <description>Frottage Blog Melee&amp;rsquo;s drawing:
I was reminded of this scene from Mulan:
Here&amp;rsquo;s some music to listen to while looking at the generations:
Music https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qAqXDZoa624&amp;amp;list=RDFPEl86wxqbs&amp;amp;index=12 Prompt Gens 1 2 a figure of a person collapses into clear water, enveloped by the splashes. cherry blossom fall from a tree into the water. pencil and watercolor 1 2 a close-up of a splash at the surface of clear water. cherry blossom petals fall from a branch into the water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Primeval Waters, Pleroma and Archons</title>
      <link>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/primeval-waters-pleroma-and-archons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/primeval-waters-pleroma-and-archons/</guid>
      <description>Some music Prompt gens 1 The pleroma_ Home of the Aeons. The World_ Home of the Archons. Digital Art 1 2 3 4 God stared down into the primeval waters and saw his reflection. The aeons tended to emanate from God in male-female pairs. Digital Art </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hobnail boots, Multicoloured Mirrors</title>
      <link>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/hobnail-boots-multicoloured-mirrors/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/hobnail-boots-multicoloured-mirrors/</guid>
      <description>Prompt 1 The man in the crowd with the multicoloured mirrors on his hobnail boots. Digital Art </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sky is Blue; Blows my Mind</title>
      <link>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/sky-is-blue-blows-my-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/sky-is-blue-blows-my-mind/</guid>
      <description>Prompt 1 The world is round. The wind is high. The sky is blue. It blows my mind. It makes me cry. Digital art </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Across the Universe</title>
      <link>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/across-the-universe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/across-the-universe/</guid>
      <description>Links Blog article https://mullikine.github.io/posts/across-the-universe/ Prompts 1 a couple kissing within a strawberry in space. stars in the background. Across the universe. Digital Art 1 a couple within a strawberry in space. stars in the background. Across the universe. Digital Art 1 a couple kissing within a strawberry in space. stars in the background. Across the universe. Digital Art 1 a couple embracing within a splat of paint in the shape of a strawberry in space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cat Playing Checkers</title>
      <link>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/cat-playing-checkers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/cat-playing-checkers/</guid>
      <description>Prompt 1 a surrealist dream-like oil painting by Salvador Dalí of a cat playing checkers </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corrupted Multiverse</title>
      <link>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/corrupted-multiverse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/corrupted-multiverse/</guid>
      <description>Hmm sounds OK Heracleitus called the Universal Principle (των απαντων αρχη) Intellectual Fire (πυρ νοερον), and said that the sphere surrounding us and reaching to the Moon was filled with evil, but beyond the Moon-sphere it was purer.
http://gnosis.org/library/grs-mead/grsm%5Fsimon%5Fmagus.htm#FNanchor%5F97
Perhaps this is to say that most of Creation isn&amp;rsquo;t corrupted. But around Earth, it kinda is. Perhaps the corruption hasn&amp;rsquo;t spread far from Earth.
DALL-E Scriptures 1 Corinthians 15:33 33 Be not deceived: evil communications corrupt good manners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fiery Red Girl</title>
      <link>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/fiery-red-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/fiery-red-girl/</guid>
      <description>Links Describing Melee&amp;rsquo;s Paintings with AlephAlpha // Bodacious Blog Imagining Melee&amp;rsquo;s artworks with DALL-E-2 // Bodacious Blog &amp;lt;3 I use DALLE to imagine my descriptions of Melee&amp;rsquo;s paintings. There is a prompt limit, so the descriptions could be improved using Imagism. However, I&amp;rsquo;m using the opening paragraph of each original description.
These generations are cool but so far nowhere accurate enough to capture the nuance of Melee&amp;rsquo;s original artworks.
Fiery red girl 1 2 3 4 5 A girl believes she must prepare for her photo to be taken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Draw a Picture</title>
      <link>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/how-to-draw-a-picture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/how-to-draw-a-picture/</guid>
      <description> Blog article https://mullikine.github.io/posts/how-to-draw-a-picture/ 1 2 3 4 To begin, select a suitable piece of paper for use, and apply pencil to same. Then, select a pencil sharpener and sharpen pencil to a suitable degree... </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian in the Cupboard</title>
      <link>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/indian-in-the-cupboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/indian-in-the-cupboard/</guid>
      <description>Poetry llamasandmystegosaurus: A description of a toy store excerpt:
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24 25 26 27 28 29 There were stranger toys, too, that I hardly know how to describe. One of them was a kind of oversized helmet attached to a microscope. It looked like it had been built around 1930 of largely cast iron parts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mad Tea-Party</title>
      <link>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/mad-tea-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/mad-tea-party/</guid>
      <description>Prompts 1 2 3 There was a table set out under a tree in front of the house, and the March Hare and the Hatter were having tea at it. Digital Art 1 2 3 4 Have some wine, _ the March Hare said in an encouraging tone. Alice looked all round the table, but there was nothing on it but tea. Digital Art 1 2 3 There was a table set out under a tree in front of the house, and the March Hare and the Hatter were having tea at it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Socrates with a Mobile Phone</title>
      <link>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/socrates-with-a-mobile-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/socrates-with-a-mobile-phone/</guid>
      <description>Prompt 1 2 Socrates holding an iPhone, photo by Henri Cartier-Bresson </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Treasure Eaters</title>
      <link>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/treasure-eaters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/treasure-eaters/</guid>
      <description>Links Blog post https://mullikine.github.io/posts/pyramid-of-the-gnosticene-ancients/ DALL-E </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Astral Staircase</title>
      <link>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/astral-staircase/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frottage.github.io/portfolio/astral-staircase/</guid>
      <description>Water, fire and light This night, as I was walking home, I passed upwards through the forest. Upon entering the forest, my vibrational energy started increasing.
It&amp;rsquo;s raining but I&amp;rsquo;m warm. I stopped, looking up the path. Behind me is single street lamp. Large rain drops dripped from the branches above. I exhaled. My warm breath went out in front of me in a cloud, illuminated by the street lamp behind me, and the large rain drops glistened in the background.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
